在本讲座中，我们将了解如何将数字图像输入计算机。
In this lecture we're going to learn about how we get a digital image into a computer.
对于机器人视觉，这是必不可少的第一步;我们必须有视觉信息
For robotic vision, this is the essential first step; we have to have the visual information
在计算机内部，以便我们可以操纵它并最终从中提取意义，
inside the computer, so that we can manipulate it and eventually extract meaning from it,
所以这是必不可少的第一步。
so this is the essential first step.
今天的数字图像非常普遍，它们无处不在。通过数十亿和数十亿美元
Digital images today are really common, they're everywhere. Through billions and billions
Facebook和Flickr上的图像，并通过Instagram等应用程序共享。那里
of images on Facebook and Flickr and shared through applications like Instagram. There
数字图像如今如此普遍的几个原因。
are a few reasons why digital images are so common today.
首先是相机无处不在，所以拍照的机会是巨大的。
The first is that cameras are everywhere so the opportunities to take pictures are enormous.
我们的手机，平板电脑，笔记本电脑都有相机。大量的
We have cameras in our phones, in our tablet computers, in our laptops. A large number
人们现在开始在他们的头上戴着相机拍摄所有的东西
of people are now starting to wear cameras on their heads photographing everything that
他们正在看到和体验，或许是24乘7。第二个原因是存储有
they're seeing and experiencing, 24 by 7 perhaps. The second reason why is that storage has
变得如此便宜。我们的手机和笔记本电脑中的低成本闪存
become so cheap. Low cost flash memory in our phones and in our laptop computers and
今天你可以用相对较少的钱购买数TB的硬盘存储空间。它
terabytes of hard disk storage that you can buy for relatively little money today. It
并不总是这样。十年前，我们正在从化学转向数字化
wasn't always this way. Ten years ago we were making the transition from chemistry to digital
拍照技术。
technology for picture taking.
在化学成像的旧时代，我们不得不在我们的电影中曝光一些画面;
In the bad old days of chemical imaging, we had to expose a number of frames on our film;
我们永远无法删除图像。一旦电影充满，我们就把它带到商店，我们会得到
we could never delete an image. Once the film was full, we'd take it to the shop, we'd get
它开发了，我们将我们的照片重新写在纸上。它的灵活性较低。所以呢
it developed and we'd get our pictures back on paper. It was way less flexible. So what
我们在这个讲座中要做的就是解决我们如何从许多人那里获取图像，
we're going to do in this lecture is work out and discuss how we get images from many,
许多数字源，可能来自您的照片库的图像，也许来自网络摄像头
many digital sources, images from perhaps your photo library, perhaps from the web camera
在您的计算机上，也许是从网络上获取这些图像到一个环境中
on your computer, perhaps from the web and getting those images into an environment where
我们可以开始操纵它们了。
we can begin to manipulate them.